<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE inex-topic-file [
<!ENTITY  lt      "lessthan">
<!ENTITY  gt      "greaterthan">
<!ENTITY  amp     "ampersand">
<!ELEMENT inex-topic-file (topic+)>
<!ELEMENT topic (title,castitle,phrasetitle,description,narrative)>
<!ATTLIST topic id CDATA #REQUIRED>
<!ATTLIST topic ct_no CDATA #REQUIRED>
<!ELEMENT title (#PCDATA)>
<!ELEMENT castitle (#PCDATA)>
<!ELEMENT phrasetitle (#PCDATA)>
<!ELEMENT description (#PCDATA)>
<!ELEMENT narrative (#PCDATA)>
]>
<inex-topic-file>
<topic id="2010001" ct_no="314">
  <title>landslide malaysia</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., landslide malaysia)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>landslides in malaysia</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about landslides that occur in Malaysia.</description>
  <narrative>I am currently working on a web portal for disseminating natural hazard information in Malaysia. One of the hazard is landslide. This portal includes information from various sources, and Wikipedia articles would be one of the contents source for our portal. For this particular search, i want to collect information about landslides that occur in Malaysia history. Results containing general definitions about landslides, such as causes, prevention, etc. are not relevant. Result elements containing landslide in other countries are not relevant. Results containing other type of natural hazards like flood in Malaysia are also not relevant. Results about landslide victory of elections in Malaysia are not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010002" ct_no="315">
  <title>search engine</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., search engine)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"search engine"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information on search engines.</description>
  <narrative>There are a lot of search engines like google, bing etc. I want to know how these search engines work.   I would be satisfied with any information given on how search engines work.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010003" ct_no="316">
  <title>Monuments of India</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Monuments) and about(., India)]//sec[about(.,Monuments of India)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Monuments" "India"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the ancient monuments in India. Their history and background.</description>
  <narrative>The sub-continent India is dotted with magnificent monuments showing the incredible artistic work and architecture. These monuments remain as the greatest legacy of the glory of the ancient Indians. These monuments were built under the reign of various emperors in India using the human labor rather than any technology. I am really fascinated by such breathtaking architecture and intricate work and would like to know more about these monuments.     For my own personal interest, I would like to learn more background about the monuments in India built in different architectural styles, in accordance to their beliefs and the history and stylistics of such great monuments.    To be relevant an element should discuss about the monuments in India and history behind it. Information on the country India alone without any information regarding the monuments is not relevant; nor is general information on Indian cultures and traditions.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010004" ct_no="318">
  <title>Indian food</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., indian food)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>" Indian food "</phrasetitle>
  <description>information about Indian food</description>
  <narrative>India is a vast country with varying cultures, languages, climates and people. Each region in India has its specific food specialty.  Cooking is my hobby and I love Indian food. I always try to cook new Indian dishes.  Following results can be considered relevant. Anything that is related to Indian food, anything related to famous hotels and their favorite dishes. Anything related to various spices, herbs, vegetables, fruits that are grown in India. Anything related to breakfast, lunch, snacks,0 beverages from India.  Following results can be considered irrelevant. The documents which is not related to Indian food anyway. Or the document that just mentions Indian food but does not contain any information related to it.  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010005" ct_no="319">
  <title>fashion</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., fashion)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"fashion"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information on fashion.</description>
  <narrative>I want to write a report on how fashion has changed over time. I want the results to have everything that is related to fashion so that I can choose topics relevant to me. The topics can range from fashion trends, fashion faux pas, popular fashion, fashion brands, etc.    Fashion also involves all the designers that are associated with fashion. Every decade has a fashion designer who has influenced the up-coming trends. Retrieval of such designer related information is also relevant to the query.    Retrieval of information on trends in different accessories or clothing is also relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010006" ct_no="320">
  <title>Evolution of Storage devices</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Evolution or History of Storage devices) or about(., "Primary or Secondary Storage devices")]//sec[about(., RAM ROM)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Evolution / History of storage devices"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the development of storage devices over time.</description>
  <narrative>A Storage device is a major component a computer system. Data has to be stored for various processing needs. With faster technology the need for better and faster storage devices is pertinent.I thought it would be interesting to know about how the storage devices changed over time to see how it catered to the needs with the evolution of technology.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010007" ct_no="322">
  <title>marilyn monroe played impersonator actor</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.//(actor|movie|play),marilyn monroe played impersonator)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"played marilyn monroe" "marilyn monroe impersonator" "impersonated marilyn monroe"  "appeared as marilyn monroe"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Looking for a Marilyn Monroe impersonator or actor who played her role</description>
  <narrative>Looking for several actors who played in the role of Maralyn Monroe to interview for a book on her legacy and the different perceptions of her.  Information about the circumstances in connection to Maralin Monroe and sufficinet information to identify the person who is reported to have acted her part is relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010008" ct_no="323">
  <title>English Literature William Wordsworth</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., English Literature)]//sec[about(., William Wordsworth )]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>English Literature "William Wordsworth"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Life of William Wordsworth and his contributions to English Literature</description>
  <narrative>Documents about English Literature in general but with a section on Wordsworth the poet is relevant.  Documents about the life and works of William Wordsworth is particularly relevant. Reviews or analysis of Wordsworth's work is also relevant. A mention to any other Wordsworth is irrelevant here.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010009" ct_no="324">
  <title>sound synthesis method</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., sound synthesis method)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"sound synthesis"  method</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find methods for sound synthesis used in musical synthesizers</description>
  <narrative>I want to know what are the methods used for sound synthesis in musical synthesizers. Some mathematics are welcome.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010010" ct_no="325">
  <title>cheese production</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., cheese production)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find methods or recipes used for cheese production</description>
  <narrative>I want to know what methods, process, recipes are used to produce cheese. What are the different steps, if heating/cooling are used, what fungi are involved, if aging is used/recommended, if some kind of milk is preferable,...</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010011" ct_no="326">
  <title>Computer "Operating Systems"</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., "operating systems")]//sec[about(., "History of operating systems") or about(., "concepts in Operating systems") or about(., "operating system")]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"operating system"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about  computer operating systems.</description>
  <narrative>operating systems in computers manage how different programs use the hardware of the system and act as an interface between user and the hardware of the system. These Operating systems are found in most of the devices which can run multiple programs. Some of the well known operating systems are  Microsoft Windows, Mac OS X, Linux, and UNIX.     After reading some technical papers about development of operating systems from the initial stage I gained some interest. I would like to know about the history of computer operating systems, how they evolved, concepts based on which they are designed, comparison between operating systems, different operating system models, examples of operating systems, and components of a operating system. I expect to find large documents which gives some clear explanation/definition of the concepts above. It is fine, if there are some sections in the article about the operating system used along with some description about it.     To be relevant the element should contain discussion about Operating system and the concepts used in it. Usage of the term "operating system" in the article with out including the name of the OS and description about it is not relevant. Just phrasing the name of the Operating system in the article is also not relevant.  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010012" ct_no="327">
  <title>Bengal Renaissance</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., "Bengal Renaissance")]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Bengal Renaissance"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Fetch documents about Bengal Renaissance period and eminent personalities during that period.</description>
  <narrative>The documents about history of and the reviews, analysis on Bengal Renaissance period is relevant. The lives and works of eminent personalities during this period is relevant too. Discussions about the upsurge of Indian Independence movement pertaining to this period is also relevant here. Information about any other renaissance period is not sought here.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010013" ct_no="328">
  <title>rock music genre</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,rock music genre)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find information about genres in rock music</description>
  <narrative>There are many genres in music. Moreover, certain genre has a lot of smaller genres. In this situation, I love to listen to rock music but I do not know well the genre in rock music. So I want to know the genres in rock music. Therefore, the relevant articles should include the genres in rock music while explanations about certain rock music are not irrelevant articles.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010014" ct_no="329">
  <title>composer museum</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., composer museum)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Documents or parts of documents that describe or identify a museum dedicated or which has a significant section dedicated to a composer</description>
  <narrative>I want to know the museum that are dedicated to or which have a significant section dedicated to a composer. Other music related museum  which are  not dedicated to a composer are not relevant (for instance a museum of musical  instruments)</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010015" ct_no="330">
  <title>rite passage transition adult</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., rite passage transition adult)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find existence and description of rites of passage to the adult status.</description>
  <narrative>I want to know what are the existing rites of passage to the adult status in different communities or culture around the world.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010016" ct_no="331">
  <title>capital punishment</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., capital punishment)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>What are the states where capital punishment is (or was applied) ? What method of execution are/were used ?</description>
  <narrative>What are the states where capital punishment is (or was) applied?  What method of execution are/were used?</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010017" ct_no="333">
  <title>lady gaga</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,lady gaga)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>lady gaga</phrasetitle>
  <description>I want to find some information about the famous singer lady gaga.</description>
  <narrative>Recently,lady gaga becomes more and more famous in students of China.So,I want to know more about lada gaga.Articles dedicated to lady gaga is relevant.Articles referring to lady gaga is irrelevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010018" ct_no="334">
  <title>Christopher Columbus and the discovery of America</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., christopher columbus america discovery)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Christopher Columbus" "America discovery"</phrasetitle>
  <description>I would like to read documents or parts of them dealing with the discovery of America by Christopher Columbus</description>
  <narrative>I like a lot the history of Spain, and one of its most important events is the discovery of America by Christopher Columbus. So I would like to have the whole sequence of events, previous and posteriorly, related to this discovery, i.e. how Columbus got the idea of reaching the Indias by the West, how he could get the corresponding financing, and all about his several trips to America, with a detail relation of the events that occurred to him in them.    Therefore, a relevant element should deal with any of the previously cited topics of interests. Any reference to America previous to Columbus is not relevant for me, as well as any other element posterior to Columbus's death.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010019" ct_no="335">
  <title>gallo roman architecture in paris</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,gallo roman architecture in paris)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"gallo roman" architecture in paris</phrasetitle>
  <description>"gallo roman" architecture in paris</description>
  <narrative>I am looking for gallo roman architecture ruins, buildings, or remains in or around Paris. Buildings that copy the gallo roman architecture are also relevant for me.  I am making a trip of few days in Paris and I like to find out where I can see such buildings.  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010020" ct_no="336">
  <title>electricity source in France</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,electricity source in France)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>electricity source in France</phrasetitle>
  <description>I am looking for information on the sources of information in France.</description>
  <narrative>I would like to know what are the sources of the electric power in France and in the metropole and also in the oversees regions of France. IAny numbers on the percentage of the different sources (nuclear, others, ...) are relevant. I am also interested in the "green" sources of electricity (wing, solar panels) and their current use in France.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010021" ct_no="337">
  <title>nazi war criminals</title>
  <castitle>//person[about(., nazi war criminals)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find information about nazi war criminals</description>
  <narrative>I'd like to collect information about nazi engaged in war crimes or crimes against humanity: who they are and which crimes they committed.  It is also interesting for me to know is they were indicted and found guilty or if they aren't still arrested.  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010022" ct_no="338">
  <title>food specialty italy</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,food specialty italy)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>food specialty italy</phrasetitle>
  <description>I am kooking for food specialty in Italy</description>
  <narrative>I am planning my holidays in Italy during the summer. I need to know the food specialities in a way to test these. Any food interest me from any region of Italy. Brands of Italian food products are also interesting because they help me to find out what food is produced there.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010023" ct_no="339">
  <title>retirement age</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., retirement age)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"retirement age"</phrasetitle>
  <description>I'd like to know the retirement age all over the world</description>
  <narrative>There will be soon a retirement reform in France, and the age of retirement will probably increase.  I'd like to know what is the retirement age in other countries. Is it the same for all people or does this age depend on the job ?  I'm also interested in the history of retirement. Since when is it possible in all countries ? How did the retirement age evolve in time ?    Information about how pensions are calculated is not relevant. Information about health and activities  of retired persons is also not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010024" ct_no="340">
  <title>mother's day</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., mother's day)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"mother's day"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about mother's day all over the world</description>
  <narrative>It will be mother's day next sunday in France. I'd like to have information about this day all over the world: how it is celebrated, what is the history of this day, and what are the related traditions.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010025" ct_no="341">
  <title>mold health</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., mold health )]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find information effect of mold on our health</description>
  <narrative>Recently Brita, which is a water cleaner, in our lab was covered with mold. Unfortunately, I should drank some molded water. So, I worry about how the mold effect our body and seek for the information. Therefore documents referring to the effect of the mold, which is fungus, are relevant while detail about the mold or referring to another meanings mold, which similar meanings to molding, are not relevant documents.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010026" ct_no="342">
  <title>american pre-columbian civilizations</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., american pre-columbian civilizations)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>american pre-columbian civilizations</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find any document, or part of it, describing any aspect of the American pre-columbian civilizations.</description>
  <narrative>I've always been interested in archeology, so I am preparing a trip to different parts of America, where archaeological remains can be visited. In order to make the decision about what countries and places to visit, I would like to read information about the pre-columbian civilizations in America, so I can know more about their culture, history, political organization, relationships or interactions among different civilizations, economy, etc., as well as the remains that can be visited in our days.     Therefore, a relevant element would be related to any aspect of any American pre-columbian civilization, and as its name explain, previously to the arrival of Christopher Columbus. Any element with a content dated in a posterior moment would be not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010027" ct_no="343">
  <title>Paul Auster</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,Paul Auster)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>I want information about the writer Paul Auster</description>
  <narrative>I want information about the writer Paul Auster. Who is he. I would get the list of books he has written and the theme of these books.   I am not interested in the prices or the way to buy these books.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010028" ct_no="344">
  <title>psychological consultation</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,psychological consultation)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>psychological consultation</phrasetitle>
  <description>I want to find some information about psychological consultation.</description>
  <narrative>I have endured a lot of pressure from work recently.So,I want to consult some famous psychologist for help.Information about any famous psychologist is relevant.But information about psychology is irrelevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010029" ct_no="346">
  <title>ballet exam</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., ballet exam)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Information regarding different kinds of ballet exams.</description>
  <narrative>I just started taking up ballet, and I want to know different ballet grade exams for different methods. The result should list the affiliated method (RAD, Russian, etc.), and how many grades are offered etc.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010030" ct_no="348">
  <title>minimaism art music</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., minimaism art music)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find any information relating to minimalistic art, including music.</description>
  <narrative>I am taking an art history class and I need to write a paper regarding what influenced minimalism, what minimalism has influenced in the field of art.     A text that describes non-minimalism art is relevant if it explains the relation between the art and the minimalism. By art, I include not only paintingish and music, but also performing art, and even novels.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010031" ct_no="349">
  <title>science women few</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., science women few)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Why are there so few women in sciences?</description>
  <narrative>I'm looking for text that describes possible causes of the scarcity of women in sciences. A text describing women in science, but not the cause of decline is irrelevant. A text describing differences in cognitive abilities of women that could be a cause, but not mentioning women in sciences is still relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010032" ct_no="350">
  <title>japanese ballerina</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., japanese ballerina)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Return a list of ballerina of Japanese descent or nationality.</description>
  <narrative>I'm compiling a list of Japanese ballet dancers. Any mention of Japanese ballet dancer, male or female, of (part) Japanese descent, or of Japanese nationality regardless of decent is relevant. Thus an article about a Japanese ballet dancer is relevant, a paragraph mentioning a Japanese ballet dancer in a totally unrelated article is relevant, and a list that only mentions the name with the occupation is also relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010033" ct_no="351">
  <title>collapse of housing bubble usa</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., collapse of housing bubble usa)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find information about the cause and impact of the USA housing bubble in 2000's.</description>
  <narrative>The economy is bad everywhere. I want to learn the cause of the current poor economy, that is the US housing bubble in 2000's and what impact it had, what caused it, and any other information that is useful in preparing for writing a paper for my economics class.    Any information pertaining to US housing bubble is relevant. Housing bubbles in other countries are only relevant if it relates to the US housing bubble. General economic theory of interest rate and housing bubbles is also useful even if it does not mention the particular US housing bubble.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010034" ct_no="353">
  <title>worm virus</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,worm virus)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>worm virus</phrasetitle>
  <description>I want to find some information about worm virus.</description>
  <narrative>I major in computer science and recently my computer infected worm virus.So I want to know how it works.Code of any kind of worm virus and what file and process some worm virus creates or modifies is relevant.Information about how to remove worm viruses is irrelevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010035" ct_no="354">
  <title>psychological effects music</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., psychological effects music)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>find information about psychological effects in music</description>
  <narrative>I'm studying psychology, especially I'm interested in the psychology of music. Any document component discussing about some musical effect on the human psyche is of interest.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010036" ct_no="355">
  <title>northern Finland languages Lapland Sami</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., northern Finland languages Lapland Sami)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find information about the languages of Lapland, northern Finland</description>
  <narrative>I'm interested in the history of Finno-Ugrian languages, which are not widely spoken anymore. Any text passage dealing with the history and usage of those languages is of interest. Examples of the languages are Sami and MeÃ¤nkieli.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010037" ct_no="356">
  <title>social network API</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,social network API)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find the information that is the related technique to social networking service.</description>
  <narrative>In recent year, social networking service (SNS) has attracted much attention. Especially, the "Facebook" and the "Twitter" have been opening aggressively their resource and had released own API. Their techniques has novel business model that is different from past major Web service such as a Web retrieving service and a portal site. Additionally, mentioned the new business model is generating the new internet industry. So, I want to information of technique about applying in SNS without technique of general Web service and non relevant to SNS.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010038" ct_no="358">
  <title>dinosaur</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., dinosaur )]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"dinosaur"</phrasetitle>
  <description>information about dinosaurs, vertebrate animals who often have enormous size</description>
  <narrative>Dinosaurs are vertebrate animals and often have enormous size. Like many others, I would like to know anything that can help scientific research on dinosaurs such as their categories, features, distinguishing behaviors, evolution, fossils, famous paleontologists who study dinosaurs, dinosaurs related museum, park, books, and geographical location. However, dinosaur fictions are not relevant, including comics, games, movie/film, and animation. Artists such as sculptors are irrelevant as well.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010039" ct_no="359">
  <title>Emmy Awards</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Emmy Awards)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>information of Emmy Awards</description>
  <narrative>I want to know something about Emmy Awards. Information, the history of Emmy Awards, awarded actors and TV program for example, is in demand.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010040" ct_no="361">
  <title>President of the United States</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., President of the United States )]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>information of President of the United States</description>
  <narrative>My nephew needs some information about the presidents of the United States for his history homework. Information, introduction of these presidents for example, is in demand.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010041" ct_no="362">
  <title>Japanese art</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Japanese art)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>information of japanese art</description>
  <narrative>Japan is a country with long history. Now, I am interested in Japanese traditional arts, flower arrangement，Bushido，Noh and tea ceremony for example. Any information about these arts will be relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010042" ct_no="363">
  <title>Quilombos settlements and leaders</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,quilombo settlement) and about(.,leader)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Quilombos settlements" "Large Quilombo" "Quilombo leaders"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Information about Quilombo history and leaders</description>
  <narrative>I'm doing some research about slaves rebellion and there influence in Brazilian history.  During my research I've heard about brazilian settlements called Quilombos who where build and ruled by escaped slaves.  I'm trying to get some informations about them: their political structure, some historical facts and their most important leaders.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010043" ct_no="364">
  <title>List of films from the surrealist category</title>
  <castitle>//movie[about(.,surrealism)]//sec[about(.,films)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Surrealist directors" "List category surrealist films"</phrasetitle>
  <description>List of films and directors related to surrealism movement</description>
  <narrative>Surrealism was an cultural movement active in various domain from  literature, to visual artwork like painting and sculture.   Sadly it seems that it only marginaly use movie direction.  As a movie-goer and big fan of the surrealistic movement I try to find a list of movies I can watch related to it.  This list must include directors and movie names directly associated and active at the begining of the movement and movies wiche are considered inspired by there codes.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010044" ct_no="365">
  <title>Tesla invention</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,tesla invention)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Tesla patent" "Tesla inventions"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Nikola Tesla inventions</description>
  <narrative>Nikola Tesla is one of XIX century major inventor. Recently recognized as so, he has been forgotten for a long time and his work stolen by others.  All these reasons make his work difficult to distinguish between reality from fiction.   For my personnal interest I try to sort out his real scientific discoveries.  Revelant items will contain a list of exact Tesla inventions and his role in the patent he developped with other famous engineers.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010045" ct_no="366">
  <title>messi argentine</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,messi argentin)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>about messi, Argentine football player</description>
  <narrative>passages that speak of information relating to Lionel Messi in football, other information on him outside the field of football are considered irrelevant.  The motivation of this research is to enable to know about the player's career in football.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010046" ct_no="369">
  <title>Meg Ryan movie</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,Meg Ryan movie)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find information about movies featuring Meg Ryan</description>
  <narrative>I like a Hollywood movie actress Meg Ryan. So I want to see her movies and search the title of them. Therefore documents referring to the movie featuring Meg Ryan are relevant while documents referring to another actress shared a name Meg Ryan, or documents referring to the movie titled Meg are not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010047" ct_no="370">
  <title>famous flute solos symphony</title>
  <castitle>//symphony//*[about(.,"flute solo")]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"flute solo" symphony</phrasetitle>
  <description>famous flute solos in symphonies</description>
  <narrative>My friend is playing the primary flute in an orchestra. I want to know, what are the most famous flute solos in symphonies. A relevant element should discuss about the matter by defining the symphony and preferably where the flute solo occurs.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010048" ct_no="371">
  <title>Pacific navigators Australia explorers</title>
  <castitle>//explorer[about(., Pacific navigators Australia explorers)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Pacific navigators" "Australia explorers"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find the navigators and explorers in the Pacific sea in search of Australia</description>
  <narrative>I am doing an essay on the explorers who discovered or        charted Australia. I am already aware of TASMAN, COOK and La        Pérouse and would like to get the full list of navigators who        contributed to the discovery of Australia. Those for who there        are disputes about their actual discovery of (parts of)        Australia are still acceptable. I am mainly interested by the        captains of the ships but other people who were on board with        those navigators still relevant (naturalists or others). I am        not interested in those who came later to settle in Australia.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010049" ct_no="372">
  <title>European fruit trees</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.//category, edible nuts and seeds) AND about(., European fruit trees)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>European "fruit trees"</phrasetitle>
  <description>I want a list of European fruit tree sorts.</description>
  <narrative>Each answer should be an article about the specific fruit tree.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010050" ct_no="373">
  <title>Novels that won the Booker Prize</title>
  <castitle>//novel[about(., Booker Prize)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>Novels that won the "Booker Prize"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find articles that describe the novels which won the prestigious booker prize.</description>
  <narrative>The user wants a list of novels that won the Booker Prize.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010051" ct_no="374">
  <title>Bond Girls</title>
  <castitle>//actor[about(., Bond Girl)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"bond girls"</phrasetitle>
  <description>I want the names of the actresses that have played the role as James Bond girl in any of the James Bond movies.</description>
  <narrative>Each answer should be an article describing the biography of each of the actresses that have been Bond girls, including the corresponding movie where they took that role.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010052" ct_no="375">
  <title>human communication revolution change</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,human communication revolution change)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"human communication" "communication revolution" change</phrasetitle>
  <description>change and revolution in the forms of human communication</description>
  <narrative>I'm reading a book on the impact of the invention of printing on mankind. This has made me interested in the different forms of human communication and when and how changes and revolutions in forms of human communication took place and what their impact was on humanity.    Articles defining human communication or describing forms of human communications are relevant. Articles stating when specific forms of human communication started are also relevant. Especially relevant are articles that also explain what impact these changes/revolutions in human communication have had.    Articles discussing non-human forms of communication are considered irrelevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010053" ct_no="376">
  <title>Hanseatic league in Germany and the Netherlands</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.//category, hanseatic league) AND about(., Germany Netherlands)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Hanseatic league" in Germany and the Netherlands</phrasetitle>
  <description>Dutch and German cities that have been part of the hanseatic league in Rhine, Westphalia, the Netherlands.</description>
  <narrative>We are interested in a list of Dutch and German cities that were member of the hanseatic league in their medieval history.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010054" ct_no="377">
  <title>Indian Railways</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Indian Railways )]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Indian Railways"</phrasetitle>
  <description>History, organizational structure, and structural details about the trains of Indian Railways</description>
  <narrative>Any information pertaining to Indian Railways - its history, its organizational structure, the technical details about the train engines and coaches, its catering services, major accidents etc. is relevant. Documents about railway systems of other countries is irrelevant here.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010055" ct_no="378">
  <title>roland garros</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,roland garros)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>roland garros tournament</description>
  <narrative>I am looking for information on the tournament and match tennis roland garros, the different editions, the main winners, the facts and the players who have marked this tournament, I did not need information about the person, or on the airport.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010056" ct_no="379">
  <title>cold war</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., "cold war")]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"cold war"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Fetch documents about the Cold War with information on the gradual buiding up of political tension between US and USSR</description>
  <narrative>Fetch documents about the long continuing cold war between US and USSR. Various impact of the cold war are also relevant. Documents about any other war is not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010057" ct_no="380">
  <title>Einstein Relativity theory</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Einstein)]//sec[about(.,relativity theory)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>Einstein "Relativity Theory"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find documents on Einstein in general containing a section on General or Special RelativityTheory</description>
  <narrative>Documents about Einstein in general with a section on General or Special Theory of Relativity is sought here. Documents about other academic achievements of Einstein is also somewhat relevant. Documents about books and films on Einstein are not relevant. Documents about religious and political views of Einstein are irrelevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010058" ct_no="382">
  <title>Lyon Railway station</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,Lyon Railway station)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>major railway stations in the city of Lyon</phrasetitle>
  <description>I need information about the major railway stations in Lyon.</description>
  <narrative>I need information about the major railway stations in Lyon. Where are they situated?   I search their names  I want to know if TGVs serve these stations.  The Lyon metro and stations of the Paris Metro are considered as Irrelevant.  I am not interested in stations situated outside of the city  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010059" ct_no="384">
  <title>Indo Pakistan relation Kargil war</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Indo Pakistan relations)]//sec[about(.,Kargil war)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>Indo Pakistan relation "Kargil war"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Retrieve documents about Indo Pakistan relations in general with a particular reference to Kargil War</description>
  <narrative>The documents discussing about the post independence relationship between the two neighboring countries is sought here. Documents about wars between the two countries is also relevant. Sections or paragraphs about the Kargil war in a document makes it highly relevant. General information about India and Pakistan in isolation is irrelevant here.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010060" ct_no="386">
  <title>American Keyboard</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,american keyboard)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find articles, which present the characteristics of American PC keyboards</description>
  <narrative>My employee wants me to learn how to use an American computer keyboard as fast as the German kind. That’s why I need information about the American keyboard, so I can find out the differences, to be well prepared when the first exercises start. Every article regarding American Keyboards are useful.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010061" ct_no="388">
  <title>dangerous paraben bisphenol-A</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., dangerous paraben bisphenol-A )]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>I want to know more on what Paraben and Bisphenol-A are dangerous and where we find them.</description>
  <narrative>I have no knowledge about Paraben and Bisphenol-A and I want to know why they are toxics. Every document's parts of a stuff which contain these components are relevants.  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010062" ct_no="390">
  <title>flower meaning</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., flower meaning)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>I want to know the meaning of flowers.</description>
  <narrative>I want to offer some flowers but I don't know their meaning. I don't want give a wrong meaning to a person. So, I am seeking the symbolism of flowers to make a bouquet.  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010063" ct_no="391">
  <title>Famous psychologists</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,famous psychologists)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>articles with information of well known psychologists.</description>
  <narrative>I am very interested in the pioneers of the psychology. That is why I want to find anything about the famous heads of this profession.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010064" ct_no="392">
  <title>image waterfall</title>
  <castitle>//image[about(.,waterfall)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>I look for images of waterfalls.</description>
  <narrative>I want to decorate my apartment with images of waterfalls. So I want to find several images of waterfalls.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010065" ct_no="393">
  <title>Guitar styles</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Guitar)]//sec[about(., style)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>I am interested in guitars in general and want to learn more about different guitar styles.</description>
  <narrative>I want to know more about guitar styles and assume an article on guitars will present at least one specific guitar style.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010066" ct_no="394">
  <title>army bases in iraq</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., army base)]//facility[about(., iraq)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>I look for locations and the historys of army bases in Iraq.</description>
  <narrative>I am writing an article about army bases in Iraq and I need information about these, like exact location and history.     </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010067" ct_no="395">
  <title>Japanese electronics companies</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Japanese)]//industry[about(., electronics)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>I want to get information about Japanese electronic companies and their most important products and strategies.</description>
  <narrative>I am writing a report about the Japanese electronic industries, the most successful companies of it and their products or strategies. So I would like to get some information about Japanese electronic products and market actions of their producers.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010068" ct_no="396">
  <title>biography of medalist in Olympic figure skating</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Olympic figure skating medal)]//sec[about(.//st, biography)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"biography" "medalist" "Olympic figure skating"</phrasetitle>
  <description>the biographical information of the Olympic medalists on figure skating</description>
  <narrative>Being a fan of figure skating, I would like to know the detailed information about the top figure skaters, particularly those who have won medals in Olympic games. I'm interested in their achievement, ranking, and career development. The insufficient information such as the list of competitions/games, names of figure skaters, references, and overview of medal counts are not relevant. Besides, the descriptions of social activities of the figure skaters which are not related to Olympic games are not interesting either.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010069" ct_no="397">
  <title>summer flowers</title>
  <castitle>//flower[about(.,summer)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find flowers that bloom in summer</description>
  <narrative>We are preparing for a street decoration feast and we would like to find out which flowers to use. These flowers should bloom in summer.  To be useful the relevant components should contain (at least) the name of the flower and state that its blooming time is in summer. Articles about flowers that do not mention the blooming time are not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010070" ct_no="398">
  <title>"tai chi" styles forms</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.//category, martial arts) AND about(., "tai chi" styles) AND about(.,"tai chi" forms)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"tai chi styles" "tai chi forms"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information on the different tai chi styles and forms.</description>
  <narrative>I am new to tai chi and, for my own interest, I would like to learn more about the different styles and forms used.    Relevant components are those that talk about any of the tai chi styles or any of the common forms used when practicing it. Also relevant are those components that discuss differences between styles. I am not interested in articles about tai chi masters or historical tai chi places. I am not interested in explanations about the tai chi movements neither.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010071" ct_no="399">
  <title>beer alcohol health effects</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., beer alcohol health effects)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>What are the effects of beer on health? Is there a difference between the different kinds/brands of beers?</description>
  <narrative>Find any information about benefits of beer on health. Which of the beers has benefits, and what are the reasons. I don't need information about alcohol effects on health in general.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010072" ct_no="400">
  <title>fisher price toys toddler</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,fisher price toys toddler)]//plaything</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>fisher price toys for toddler</phrasetitle>
  <description>I am looking for information about toys for toddler by Fisher Price.</description>
  <narrative>I am looking for some good quality toys produced by Fisher-Price for my toddler. I try to look up Wiki for description about the concept and purpose of the toys in order to help me with my toys selection. Some toys of my interest include Roll-a-Rounds, Little People, Doodle Pro etc. Results describing the founder, company or news about Fisher Price are not relevant. Results featuring toys from other companies are not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010073" ct_no="401">
  <title>bee disparition</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., bee disparition)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Want get information on disparition of bees in the world.</description>
  <narrative>Want get information on disparition of bees in the world. How large is the phenomena? What are the hypothesis about why ? Are all species of bees concerned?</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010074" ct_no="402">
  <title>famous people on postage stamps</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., famous people on postage stamps)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"famous people" "postage stamps"</phrasetitle>
  <description>I want to study how people end up as the subjects of postage stamps. I need information about the actual stamp issues, postal authority (country), denomination, year of issue, name of the person.</description>
  <narrative>Relevant passages identify the subject on the stamp and the country or postal authority that issued the stamp. Additional information about the stamp is also relevant: year of issue and denomination, or an image of the stamp. Information about similar stamps is helpful if the similar stamps are about famous personalities. A person is supposedly famous if they appear on a stamp.  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010075" ct_no="403">
  <title>volcanic ash cloud flight disruption</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., volcanic ash cloud flight disruption)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>volcanic, ash, cloud, "flight disruption"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Why should planes avoid volcanic ash?</description>
  <narrative>I am interested in information about volcanic ash clouds that caused flight disruptions or incidents in the past. Anything that tells me what's wrong with flying through ash clouds is relevant, be it technical explanations or examples of incidents that occurred.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010076" ct_no="404">
  <title>ultra marathon running</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., ultra marathon running)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find information about ultra marathon running: definition, races and other events, etc.</description>
  <narrative>Find information about ultra marathon running. I'd like to find some information about ultra running (what is it) and about ultra races around the world. I don't need information about marathon or shorter distances races, neither about clubs or athletes (except if the bio includes some details about the races).</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010077" ct_no="406">
  <title>image jacues brel concert</title>
  <castitle>//image[about(.,jacques brel in concert)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>images of Jacques Brel related to his concerts</description>
  <narrative>Jacques Brel is a very famous Belgian singer of French songs. He wrote some very special songs that still are very famous, the most famous one was "Ne me quitte pas". He also was a very strong life performer.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010078" ct_no="407">
  <title>concert and show of Beatles</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.//category, Beatles)]//sec[about(., concert) or about(.,show)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"concert" "show" "Beatles"</phrasetitle>
  <description>concert and show information of the Beatles</description>
  <narrative>Being the famous English rock band, the Beatles has made its history for popular music. To understand their popularity, we can have some impression from shows and concerts where they appeared. The size of audience, reactions from audience, comments on the concert and concert location are relevant. The name of songs and roles they played are also interesting. But we are not interested in canceled Shows and lists of track or show.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010079" ct_no="408">
  <title>famous chess endgames</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.//category, chess)]//sec[about(., endgame) or about(.,famous)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>what are the famous chess endgames</description>
  <narrative>The endgame in chess requires special skills from the player. Sometimes players are far better in this phase of the game than the phases before. It is important to know what makes a position winning in the ending phase of the game.  Examples of typical positions are useful to train the improvement of chess playing skills. A broad overview will learn the chess player to recognize the relevant characteristics of a winning endgame position.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010080" ct_no="409">
  <title>machine translation</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., machine translation)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"machine translation"</phrasetitle>
  <description>information about machine translation</description>
  <narrative>I am now at my first year of PHD. My research interest is machine translation. It is an application area of natural language processing. Now I want to learn as much as possible about machine translation.  Information about papers, articles, schools, principles, researchers, research institutes and other information which will be good for my study are relevant.   Information about translation rules for those translators, which have nothing to do with machine, is irrelevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010081" ct_no="410">
  <title>frederick jelinek</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,frederick jelinek)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"frederick jelinek"</phrasetitle>
  <description>information about the famous researcher frederick jelinek</description>
  <narrative>I am very interested about the famous natural language processing expert---frederick jelinek.  Information about frederick jelinek, his research, his laboratory, his anecdote, his students, his co-workers are all relevant.   Information about other people whose surname is also jelinek is irrelevant.  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010082" ct_no="411">
  <title>Larry Hsien Ping Lang</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,Larry Lang) or about(., Hsien Ping Lang)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Larry Lang" "Hsien Ping Lang"</phrasetitle>
  <description>information about the famous economist Larry Hsien Ping Lang</description>
  <narrative>I am very interested about the famous economist-- Larry Hsien Ping Lang. He is the best economist in our country, China.  Information about Larry Lang, his research, his experiences, his anecdote, his interviews, his shows are all relevant.   Information about other people whose surname is Lang is irrelevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010083" ct_no="412">
  <title>the history of Stanford University</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,Stanford University)]//sec[about(.,history)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Stanford University history"</phrasetitle>
  <description>information about the history of the famous Stanford University</description>
  <narrative>Recently, I have read an article about the reason why Stanford University has fostered so many successful entrepreneurs in Silicon Valley. So, I become very interested about the history of Stanford University.  Information about the history of the university is relevant. Information about other aspect of the university is irrelevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010084" ct_no="413">
  <title>Google scholar</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,Google Scholar)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Google Scholar"</phrasetitle>
  <description>information about Google Scholar</description>
  <narrative>I have used the service of Google Scholar for over 4 years since it came into being. The service of Google scholar is always improving. It benefits our life so much.  Any Information about Google scholar is relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010085" ct_no="414">
  <title>mountain bike</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,mountain bike)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"mountain bike"</phrasetitle>
  <description>information about mountain bike</description>
  <narrative>Recently, I have decided to go to lab everyday by bike. As there is a long way to ride, I decided to by a mountain bike. And now I want to know as much as possible about mountain bike.  Information about the history, brands, structure, experiences about mountain bike is relevant. Sports contests about mountain bike are relevant, too.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010086" ct_no="415">
  <title>highest mountain peaks in North America</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,highest mountain peaks in north america)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"highest mountain peaks" "North America"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the highest mountain peaks in North America</description>
  <narrative>I love the mountains, and conquering their highest peaks is always a challenge for me.   Since I plan on going in the US, I would like to use the opportunity and visit some of the highest peaks there.  In order to do that first I need to find out who they are, and then to continue the research on few of them individually.  Relevant documents or document parts are those that provide a (sort of) list of the highest peaks of North America, and/or discuss about some of them individually.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010087" ct_no="417">
  <title>technological singularity</title>
  <castitle>//sec[about(., technological singularity)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"technological singularity"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the concept of technological singularity and its implications.</description>
  <narrative>I am in the process of writing a book about technological singularity. For this purpose, I want to find as much relevant information as possible about this concept, including its implications on various aspects of our society: life, religion, science and the broad understanding of our universe. Relevant documents should primarily focus on the concept of technological singularity and its related (derived) concepts and future implications, describing either scientific (popular) articles or science fiction books related to the topic. Documents describing biographies of popular scientists and thinkers related to the concept of technological singularity are not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010088" ct_no="418">
  <title>"Apple Inc" products invented by "Steve Jobs"</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., "Apple Inc") or about(., invented by "Steve Jobs")]//sec[about(., Apple products)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Apple Inc products" "Steve Jobs"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about Apple products invented by Steve Jobs</description>
  <narrative>Story of Apple Inc. fascinates me. Apple defined the personal computing the way do it today for the first time over 25 year ago. I want to know the list of products invented by Steve Jobs which helped in success of Apple Inc. Articles about history of Apple while emphasizing on contributions by Steve Jobs. and how they impacted in the success/failure of Apple inc.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010089" ct_no="419">
  <title>European free jazz</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,europian free jazz)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Europian free Jazz" "free jazz music" "history of europian free jazz"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the history of european jazz music.</description>
  <narrative>For my own personal interests, I want to know about beginnings i.e. history of european free jazz music. I wonder which instruments are used in european free jazz. Also, I want to know who are european free improvisers.   Documents should be relevant if they provide information about beginnings of free jazz in Europe (with years), contain list of instruments that are used or provide information about founders of the free jazz music in Europe.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010090" ct_no="420">
  <title>Formula for academic ranking of universities in the world</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,formula for academic ranking of universities in the world)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"academic ranking of universities" "formula for academic ranking of universities" "world" "wordwide"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the proces (formula) for academic ranking of universities in the world.</description>
  <narrative>I want to know which universities in the world are best ranked. For my own personal interests, I wonder which institution is privileged to do the ranking, and how the criteria and formula for ranking are defined. Also, I want to know how many worldwide universities are into the process of academic ranking. Retrieved documents should be relevant if they provide information about the academic ranking process of universities (formula or criteria) and they should contain a list of best ranked worldwide universities   (probably 5 to 10).</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010091" ct_no="421">
  <title>jane austen movies</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., jane austen movies)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Jane Austen" "filmography" "films" "movies"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the movies (films) based on Jane Austen novels.</description>
  <narrative>I am impressed by Jane Austen novels (books). Also, I have seen some movies based on her popular love stories. I am interested to find information about all the movies based on her literature work which exist or are in production. Relevant documents or document parts should list all movies or TV series of this kind, or they should contain some information about plot, genre, release date and maybe actors. Documents or document parts that contain information about Jane Austen bibliography, family tree, time-line, or book clubs, are not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010092" ct_no="422">
  <title>Drum and bass music</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., Drum and bass music)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Drum and bass" "Drum 'n bass" "DnB" "Drum &amp; bass"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find infromation about the electronic genre in the music drum and bass.</description>
  <narrative>I am a big fan of the Drum and bass electronic music style. I want to know more about the beginnings of this type of electronic music, its influences as a music style, and the history of the rhythm development in the drum and bass style. Also I want to know about the pioneers of this kind of music style. Retrieved documents or document parts are relevant if they provide information about the history of this style of music, all the drum and bass DJs, bands and developers, the most famous drum and bass events, and the equipment required for producing this kind of music. Documents or document parts containing information about one single instrument (drum kit or bass guitar) are not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010093" ct_no="423">
  <title>Tose Proeski humanitarian work</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., Tose Proeski humanitarian work)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Tose Proeski" "humanitarian work"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about Tose Proeski's humanitarian work</description>
  <narrative>Tose Proeski was the most popular Macedonian singer across the entire Balkan and further. He was especially known for his strong vocal performances and his precious humanitarian work. During his lifetime, Proeski held numerous humanitarian concerts for several  reasons (he died in a car accident at the age of 26).   I am a big fan of Tose's work and I am fascinated of his activities, and so I would like to get more information about all his humanitarian work. This information would help me realize my intention in writing an article about it.  Relevant documents or document parts should discuss about humanitarian concerts and all fund-raising events that were organised by Tose Proeski. Documents or document parts discussing about his biography, his songs and albums are not relevant.  </narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010094" ct_no="424">
  <title>Chapters of Hells Angels MC</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., Chapters of Hells Angels MC)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Hells Angels" "Chapters of Hells Angels" "Motorcycle club"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about official chapters of Hells Angels MC outside of the U.S.</description>
  <narrative>I am big motorcycle enthusiast. I have been at some local and closely international motorcycle events. I am interested to find information about all official chapters of Hells Angels MC outside of the U.S.  Relevant retrieved documents and document parts should provide a list of Hells Angels chapters or details about some of them (places, date joined, number of members etc.).  Documents or document parts that contain information about history or activities of Hells Angels MC are not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010095" ct_no="425">
  <title>Jazz "Charles Mingus" "Miles Davis" collaboration interaction personal relationship -album</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Charles Mingus )]//sec[about(., Miles Davis ) and about(.,-album) and about(.,relation)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Charles Mingus" "Miles Davis" "jazz collaboration" "personnal relation between Charles Mingus and Miles Davis"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the musical and personnal relation between Charles Mangus and Miles Davis other than albums.</description>
  <narrative>For my own personal interest, I would like to learn more background about the relationship between the two Jazz icons Charles Mingus and Miles Davis other that their common albums. I'm specially interested in the point of view of Charles Mingus about Miles Davis.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010096" ct_no="426">
  <title>predictive analysis +logistic +regression model program application</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,predictive analysis) and about(.,regression) and about(.,logistic)]//*[about(.,model) or about(.,program) or about(.,application)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"predictive analysis" "logistic regression" "logistic regression model" "programming logistic regression" "logistic regression applications"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about implementations and applications of logistic regression and closely related methods .</description>
  <narrative>I know logistic regression but I don't understand why is so widely used. I want to study the similarities among its numerous applications and why this type of predictive analysis is often favored. Detailed aspects about logistic regression technique are not useful, neither too narrow applications. Information relating logistic regression to other approaches of predictive analysis is welcomed.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010097" ct_no="427">
  <title>health risk coca leaf</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,health risk)]//*[about(.,coca leaf)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"health risk" "coca leaf" "traditional coca leaf consumption" "health study"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Any information about health implication of traditional coca leaf consumption.</description>
  <narrative>I'm trying to figure out if shewing coca leafs or drinking coca tea is more unhealthy than drinking coffee or tea. Information about cocaine consumption are not relevant, neither is information about reasons of coca leaf consumption.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010098" ct_no="428">
  <title>world history irvine university braudel</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,world history) or about(.,irvine university)]//*[about(.,braudel)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"world history" "Irvine University" "Fernand Braudel"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Any information about the relationship between World History as defined at Irvine University and the work of Fernand Braudel.</description>
  <narrative>I know quite well the work of the French historian Fernand Braudel ant its ideas about a global history but I've just discovered the Californian school of World History. The two approaches show many similarities and I would like to know if Braudel had an influence on the development of this theory. Details on Braudel's work are only relevant if they are related to world history.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010099" ct_no="430">
  <title>quakers slavery william penn slaves segregation segregated meetings feminism homosexuality debate</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(.,quakers slavery william penn slaves segregation segregated meetings feminism homosexuality)]//sec[about(.,debate)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>quakers slavery "william penn slaves" segregation "segregated meetings" feminism homosexuality debate</phrasetitle>
  <description>Any information about the debates among Quakers before they reached consensus about feminism, slavery, segregation and homosexuality.</description>
  <narrative>The religious society of friends is well known for its progressive positions on feminism, slavery, segregation and homosexuality. But before reaching these consensual positions, it seems that debates among themselves were sharp. By way of example, William Penn owned some slaves in America, as did many other Quakers. I want to learn about this process. General information about quakers is not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010100" ct_no="431">
  <title>house concrete wood</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(.,house construction)]//sec[about(.,concrete wood)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"concrete house" "wooden house"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Which is better, concrete house or wooden house?</description>
  <narrative>In countries like India and France, we mostly have houses made of cement brick and mortar. In the USA and Canada homes are mostly made of wood. Why these differences and which home is actually a better ?</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010101" ct_no="432">
  <title>Project Gutenberg</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., project gutenberg)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Project Gutenberg"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find documents on the project Gutenberg</description>
  <narrative>Complete articles on Project Gutenberg and its local sister projects are relevant. Documents with "Gutenberg" in any other sense such as the bible are not relevant.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010102" ct_no="433">
  <title>International Art Crime</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., International Art Crime ) or about(., Art theft ) ]//sec[about(., International Art Crime) or about(., Art Crime Research)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"International Art Crime"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the famous international art crimes and research programs on art crimes</description>
  <narrative>Art theft is the theft of art. This is usually done for the purpose of resale or ransom; occasionally thieves are also commissioned by dedicated private collectors. Stolen art is sometimes used by criminals to secure loans.    I am looking for a historical events in Art theft and any significant measures taken by any governament to curb international art crime. And also if there any research or studies related to International Art Crime.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010103" ct_no="434">
  <title>Brain Tumors</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., "Brain Tumor") or about(., "Brain Cancer") ]//sec[about(., Surgery) or about(., Chemotherapy)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"Brain Tumor" "Brain Cancer"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the Brain tumors and treatment options</description>
  <narrative>Brain Tumor is one of the deadliest diseases, which kills thousands of people all over the world. I this query I want to know about "Brain Tumor" and the treatment options like surgery and chemorherapy available for it.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010104" ct_no="435">
  <title>Indian Nobel laureates</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., India) or about(., Nobel prize winners) ]//sec[about(., Nobel laureates of India)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>"India" "Nobel Prize Winners"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the Indian Nobel laureates</description>
  <narrative>I want to know about Indian nobel prize winners from all disciplines.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010105" ct_no="436">
  <title>Gulf Oil Spill</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., Oil Spills) or about(., Oil Disasters) ]//sec[about(., "Gulf Oil Spill")]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle>Gulf "Oil Spill"</phrasetitle>
  <description>Find information about the Oil spills in Gulf in the past</description>
  <narrative>I want to know about all the gulf oil spills, the reasons for the spill and actions taken.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010106" ct_no="437">
  <title>organic food advantages disadvantages</title>
  <castitle>//*[about(., organic food advantages disadvantages)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Find advantages and disadvantages of organic food.</description>
  <narrative>I want to live healthier, and many health advocates support organic food. However, a lot of studies about organic food I hear on news today say there is no particular advantages in consuming organic food. Hence, I would like to decide if it is worth spending money on organic food.</narrative>
</topic>
<topic id="2010107" ct_no="438">
  <title>factors determining human height</title>
  <castitle>//article[about(., human)]//p[about(., factors determining height)]</castitle>
  <phrasetitle/>
  <description>Explain factors that determine adult human height.</description>
  <narrative>Most of the members of my family and relatives are tall for their age/gender/ethnicity. But a few of them are short. I'd like to know how that came about. Is this malnutrition, or one short gene sneaking around? A passage that describes anything that determines adult human height is relevant. A passage that describes correlation of a human trait with a human height is only relevant if there is a possibly causation. For example, a passage that describes the correlation between human IQ and height is not relevant because the tone of the article implies that height increase causes higher IQ, as opposed to vice versa.</narrative>
</topic>
</inex-topic-file>
